{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Máng" ,
      "answer": "忙"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bàba",
      "answer": "爸爸"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ma" ,
      "answer": "吗"
    },
    {
      "question": "Māmā",
      "answer": "妈妈"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tāmen",
      "answer": "他们"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tā",
      "answer": "他"
    },
    {
      "question": "men",
      "answer": "们"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dōu",
      "answer": "都"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bù",
      "answer": "不"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nán",
      "answer": "男"
    },
    {
      "question": "Péngyǒu",
      "answer": "朋友"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ne",
      "answer": "呢"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gēgē",
      "answer": "哥哥"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yào",
      "answer": "要"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kāfēi",
      "answer": "咖啡"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dìdì",
      "answer": "弟弟"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hē",
      "answer": "喝"
    }
  ]
}
